Guide to the Atlanta Lesbian Feminist Alliance Archives, ca. 1972-1994 RL.00022
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Other Feminist Organizations Series
  - WRFG (Radio Free Georgia) files
    - Audio Materials
      - 7" reel-to-reel tapes
        - And I'm One of Them (Box 27)
        - Dr. Donnie Bellamy (Box 27)
        - Mabel Vernon (Box 27)
        - Occupation: Coal Miner (Box 27)
        - Wilma Von Dusseldorp/New Deal (Box 27)
        - Women and Men, Part 3 (Box 27)
        - Women on the Global Assembly Line (Box 27)
        - Women's Political Caucus (Box 27)
      - 10.5" reel-to-reel tapes
        - Emma Goldman (Box 26)
        - The Muse of Lesbians T/O (Box 26)
        - Coal Mining Women/An Ordinary Morning (Box 26)
      - Audiocassettes (Box 28)
        - From a Woman's Perspective: A New Radio Series (7 cassettes), 1985-1986 (Box 28)
        - Feminization of Poverty, 1984 (Box 28)
        - New Voices--Women in Development--Public Interest Video Network, 1988 (Box 28)
        - Gayle Marie, 1985 (Box 28)
        - Fits and Starts: An Exhibition Starting to Fit: A Multimedia Work (Box 28)
        - Meg Christian interview, 1980 (Box 28)
        - Today in Georgia, 5/4/78, 1978
        - Women's International News Gathering Service (WINGS), 27 cassettes, 1987-1991 (Box 28)
    - Program Files
      - Copy for broadcasts of the Atlanta Women's New Collective (Box 25)
      - Press releases, etc. to be excerpted for broadcast (Box 29)
      - Program notes: From a Woman's Perspective, #6-9 (Box 29)
      - WINGS program notes, 1987-1990 (Box 29)
      - KPFA The Feminization of Poverty promotional material, 1984 (Box 29)
      - Judy Roberts, jazz artist, promotional material (Box 29)
      - HerSay: A Women's News service, correspondence and program notes, 1977-1989
  - Womonwrites (Lesbian Writers and Publishers Conference)
    - Planning and evaluation materials, 1979-1992 (Box 29)
  - Southern Women's Music and Comedy Festival
    - Festival materials, 1986-1988 (Box 29)
- Oversize Materials
  - Posters and Photos: Alfa Specific (Oversize-folder 1)
  - Posters: Original Art, Georgia Human Rights Campaign Fund (Oversize-folder 2)
  - Posters and Photos (Oversize-box 1, Folder 3)
  - Posters and Photos: Alfa Specific (Oversize-box 1, Folder 4)
  - Posters: Original Art (Miscellaneous) (Oversize-box 1, Folder 5)
  - Posters: Lucinas Music and Orchid Productions (Oversize-box 1, Folder 6)
  - Posters: Women's Movement (Atlantic Area) (Oversize-box 1, Folder 7)